Hello everyone,
大家好
I am Wang Jingkun,
我是王景坤
I will introduce you to the statistical learning
今天给大家介绍统计学习方法
method today. Computers and networks have been integrated
计算机与网络已融入了人们的
into people's daily work and life,
日常学习工作和生活之中
and become indispensable assistants and partners. The
成为人们不可或缺的助手和伙伴
rapid development of computers and networks
计算机与网络的飞速发展
has completely changed people's learning and lifestyle.
完全改变了人们的学习工作和
Intelligentization
生活方式
is a major goal of computer research and
智能化是计算机研究与开发的
development. Practices in
一个主要目标
recent decades have shown that statistical
近几十年来的实践表明
learning methods are the most effective means of
统计学习方法是实现这一目标的
achieving this goal,
最有效手段
although it still has certain limitations. The author
尽管它还存在着一定的局限性
has been engaged in the research of various intelligent
作者一直从事利用统计学习方法
processing of text data using statistical learning
对文本数据进行各种智能性处理
methods.
的研究